Zachary Hervieux-Moore

Profile

Applied scientist researching deep reinforcement learning and its applications. My goal is to expand the current methods to a larger class of settings and apply them to robotics

Contact

Phone. (609) 608-0336 ztjh@alumni.princeton.edu hervature.com

Skills

Programming:

Python, C++

Machine Learning Frameworks: PyTorch, Jax, Pandas, scikit-learn

Software:

Git, LaTeX

Cloud: AWS - EC2, S3, IAM, PCluster

Languages:

English, Spanish, French

Education

Princeton University

2016-2021

- PhD, Operations Research and Financial Engineering
- Master's, Operations Research and Financial Engineering
- Thesis: Modern Reinforcement Large Action Spaces

Queen's University

2011-2016

- Bachelor of Science Engineering, Mathematics and Engineering,
- Bachelor of Arts, Economics
- Thesis: Region Tracking in a Sequence of Images

Experience

Amazon, Las Vegas, NV Senior Applied Scientist

2022-Present

- -Lead a team of 8 scientists and engineers that develop reinforcement learning solutions across the whole company.
- -Created a deep reinforcement learning approach that achieves optimal bin-packing performance given the constraints of a robot.
- —Developed the optimization portion of a reinforcement learning approach to the core selection problem.
- -Built the internal infrastructure the team uses to train and deploy solutions.

Harvard University, Cambridge, MA

2021-2022

Postdoctoral Researcher

- -Worked with Francesca Dominici to develop a deep learning model to predict the amount of wildfire smoke for the USA everyday based on satellite imagery.
- -Worked with Natesh Pillai to develop a reinforcement learning approach to learn improved MCMC algorithms.

Correlation One, NYC, NY

2019-2021

Data Scientist

- -Developed and taught course material on the following topics: machine learning, deep learning, and reinforcement learning.
- -Was the head teaching assistant for 8 editions of the Data Science For All course with two editions being taught in Colombia & Brazil.
- -Regularly taught on all topics of the Data Science For All course to a total of 10k students. Was the lead instructor for two editions of their Amazon training course.

Stratyfy, NYC, NY **Data Scientist**

2018-2019

- -Developed a novel discretisation algorithm that boosted our models' performance to match state of the art techniques.
- -Wrote technical and non technical case studies of our methodology that are used to pitch customers, investors, or published online.
- -Built internal tools written in Python to automate the process of transitioning customers to our machine learning platform.

Siemens Healthineers, Princeton, NJ

Summer 2017

Business Program Intern

- -Responsible for the formulation and development of the underlying algorithm used in a scheduling application.
- -Programmed in Python using Pandas to manipulate the data and CPLEX to model and solve the optimization problem.
- -Researched deep learning and reinforcement learning to create a novel scheduling algorithm.

Altera (now Intel PSG), San Jose, CA Software/Hardware Engineer Intern

2014-2015

- -Maintained and improved internal test infrastructure.
- -Regularly coded Perl firmware and Django web applications. Automated the deployment of infrastructure using Puppet.
- -Modernized the test infrastructure by upgrading the OS and refactoring code to utilize the latest stable release of various software packages.